Giorgi Kartsivadze



qarcigio444@mail.ru



linkedin.com/in/gkartsivadze16



https://gkartsivadze.github.io/

Summary

Hello, I'm a self-motivated learner in front-end development, and I hope to pursue a career in this field. I have been learning for two years, and I work hard every day to improve my coding skills.

I am passionate about this field, and I believe I would be a good fit for any relevant job opportunity. I enjoy taking on new challenges in each project I undertake and find it rewarding to solve them, as it helps me to grow and develop my abilities. At the moment I'm learning PHP in addition.

Programming has been a lifelong dream of mine, and now I feel ready to turn it into a career.

Experience



Electrician

Naftomar Shipping And Trading Co. Ltd. Inc. Sep 2022 - Dec 2022 (4 months)

Assistant Electrician

Naftomar Shipping And Trading Co. Ltd. Inc. Nov 2021 - Apr 2022 (6 months)

Waiter

Best Western® Hotels & Resorts Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Mechanical Technician

Scroll

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021 (3 months)

Waiter

Rosso

May 2021 - Jul 2021 (3 months)

Education



Batumi State Maritime Academy

Bachelor's degree, Electromechanical Engineering Aug 2018 - Aug 2022

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • SASS • JavaScript • jQuery • Responsive Web Design • Git • Application Programming Interfaces (API) • Adobe Photoshop • Microsoft Visual Studio Code